环球影业
翻译： CJ 我爱吃榴莲 wiji
康卡斯特旗下子公司
校对：CJ  精校：Wlder 监制：我爱吃榴莲
后期：Ethan Rao
暗黑宇宙系列
完 美 世 界 影 视
死亡是通往新生的大门 吾辈活在当下 亦当得以重生 以多种形式回归世间
——古埃及复活祷词
完美影业 暗黑宇宙系列合作
共同呈现
英格兰
公元 1127年
英 国
现 如 今
这到底是什么鬼东西
What the hell is this?
我不知道
I don't know.
真是见了鬼了
Bloody hell.
横贯地铁线是欧洲最大的建设工程
The crossrail is the biggest construction project in europe.
伦敦  直播
地 铁 建 设 惊 现 古 代 遗 迹
总长26英里的全新市郊往返地铁隧道
Carving 26 miles of new commuter train tunnels.
BBC新闻
将会贯穿整个伦敦的地底
Beneath the surface of London.
但是今天 一个摆满着十字军骑士棺材的
But today, an ancient tomb filled with.
古代墓穴被隧道挖掘队发现
the coffins of crusader night have unearth…
人们不知道的是 伦敦是个巨大的墓地
People don't realize that London is a giant graveyard.
一座建立在世代亡魂上的现代都市
A modern city built on centuries of death.
教授 罗宾 约翰逊 考古学部门
由于古墓的位置靠近泰晤士河
Because of the tombs proximity to the thames…
一半以上的空间已经遭河水灌满 是这样吗 教授
…half the space is flooded, is that right doctor?
是的 水下还有更多墓棺等着我们去挖掘
There are even more coffins submerged under water.
墓棺看起来像是
The tomb appears to have been built.
在第二次十字军远征期间修建的
during the second crusade.
这也就说明墓棺里都是
…which means it's filled with the bodies.
在我们祖先回到英格兰之前
of crusader knights to invade the Egypt.
那些入侵埃及的十字军骑士
…before we returning to England.
这也打开了地底世界
It has also revealed a treasure trove.
的神秘宝库
of secrets about have unearthed…
请把场子给清了
Clear them out, please.
女士们先生们 请停下你们手上的工作
Ladies and gentlemen, please stop what you are doing.
地铁线路已重新规划到了北边儿
The train tunnel has been rerouted north of here.
我们现在开始接管这个遗迹
We are now taking control of this site.
请收拾好你们的设备快速离开这片区域
Please collect your tools and gear and exit immediately.
喂
Ohy!
不好意思 先生 先生
Excuse me. excuse me.
这片区域已经封锁了 你还在这干什么
This is my site. what do you think you are doing?
叫你的人撤离 这片遗迹现在由我们来接管
Evacuate your men. we'll take it from here.
你们都是些什么人
Who the hell are you people?
这边请 先生 非常感谢您的配合
This way, sir. thank you very much.
过去不可能被永久地埋藏
The past cannot remain buried forever.
我的这一生 已经发掘出
In my lifetime, I have unearth…
许许多多的古代未解之谜
…many ancient mysteries.
终于 这座古墓
At last, this tomb…
揭示了古代最黑暗的秘密
…reveals antiquities darkest secret.
一段被抹去的历史
A secret erased from history…
被时间忘却的秘密 终于被我找到了
…and forgotten to time.
安玛奈特公主
Princess Ahmanet.
貌美如花
Beautiful…
奸诈狡猾
…cunning…
冷酷无情
…and ruthless.
古埃及王朝的唯一继承人
Sole heir to the throne of egypt.
法老王朝终有一日会由她来统领
The pharaohs kingdom will one day be hers to rule…
笼罩在她那恐怖的暴政之下
…without mercy or fear.
安玛奈特也会被当作神祇在世般 受到人民的崇拜
And Ahmanet would be worshipped as a living god.
但是 法老有了一个儿子
But pharaoh had a son.
这个男孩 将会承继她的命运
The boy now, would inherit her destiny.
安玛奈特也明白 权利不能是授予而来
And Ahmanet understood power was not given…
而是要通过手段掠夺而来
…it had to be taken.
她对神发誓要复仇
Vowing revenge…
她选择了信奉邪恶
…she made a choice to embrace evil.
赛斯
Seth.
古埃及的死神
The god of death.
他们签订下了契约
They made a pact.
这个契约会释放黑暗的本源
A pact that would unleash darkness itself.
安玛奈特得到了重生
Ahmanet was reborn…
一个恶魔
…a monster.
不过 契约并没就此结束
Yet the pact was not complete.
她发誓要把这只恶魔带到人间
She vowed to bring the demon into our world…
附身到一个凡人的身上
…in the body of a mortal man.
一起 他们会将复仇之火降临到人类的头上
Together, they would take their vengeance upon humanity.
为了赎罪 安玛奈特被活生生做成了木乃伊
For her sins, Ahmanet was mummified alive.
她的遗体被带到了远离埃及的地方
Her body carried far from egypt.
在那 她会饱受无尽黑暗的包围和指责
There she would remain, condemned to eternal darkness.
但死亡 只是通向复活的另一道大门
But death is a doorway…
过去也不可能被永久地埋藏
…and the past cannot remain buried forever.
新 木 乃 伊
美索不达米亚
文明的摇篮
如今名曰伊拉克
运气不怎么好啊 中士
Out of luck, ah sarge?
平民都跑了
The civilians are gone.
现在那地方只剩一堆叛乱分子了
Is filled with insurgents down there.
我猜我们来的太晚了
I guess we're too late.
伊拉克
摩苏尔
亲爱的珍妮弗
调查古遗迹
哈拉姆
北纬
恭呈
亨利
我们一定能找到的
We can do this.
噢不不不 我们太迟了
Oh no no no! we're too late!
指挥部以为我们在离这里一百英里的地方
Command thinks we are doing advanced recon…
进行深入敌后的侦查任务
…a 100 miles from here.
中士 你不能去那个地方
Sarge, you are not going down there.
对 我不能 我们要一起去
You're right. i'm not. we are.
- 我们起码得叫个空袭吧 - 空袭
- at least call in an air strike. - air strike?
馊主意
Bad idea.
就丢一个炸弹 没准他们就被全部吓跑了
A little one. just maybe they'll run off.
然后我们的行踪就暴露啦
And the command will know where we are.
然后我们就会因为打劫罪
And then we will do 20 years.
在堪萨斯州的莱文沃斯堡（监狱）蹲上20年
in leavenworth for looting.
我怎么跟你说的 我们不是劫匪
Hey, what did I tell you? hey, we are not looters.
我们是珍稀古文物的解放者
We are liberators of precious antiquities.
- 对 - 对头
- right. - right.
但我们根本不知道那埋着什么
But we don't even know what's down there.
哈拉姆 那下面就埋着哈拉姆 稀有宝藏
Haram. haram is what's down there. treasure.
不 翻译说哈拉姆意思是「被禁止的知识」
No, the translator said "haram" means "forbidden knowledge".
比如说诅咒
Like a curse.
在这个地方 这种词就代表着另外一个意思「宝藏」
Around here that's just another word for "treasure."
而这个叫亨利的家伙
And this guy, this… Henry guy…
看起来想要这个宝藏快想疯了
…it seems to want it pretty bad.
现在 看来他要付双倍价才能把这个宝藏搞到手
Well… now he is gonna have to pay double.
- 上马 准备出发 - 长官 我拒绝这次行动
- mount up. - "no, sir, I ain't going on this one."
- 什么 - 我拒绝
- what? - i'm not going.
韦尔
Vail.
你想干嘛 用那捅我吗
What are you going to do? "stab me with that?"
噢 不不不 不
Oh no no no no… no!
你就是个神经病
You crazy bastard.
到下个水源点之前 这可是我一天骑行的饮水量啊
It's a full days ride to the nearest water!
最近的水源 就在下面那个村子里
The nearest water is right down in that village.
拜托 韦尔
Come on, Vail.
你的冒险精神去哪啦
Where is your sense of adventure?
噢 这真棒啊 太棒了
Oh that's just great, nick! that's just great!
来嘛 我们就像往常一样潜入进去 神不知 鬼不觉
Come on, we slip in - slip out, just like we always do.
你个狗娘养的
You son of a bitch!
我滴神也
Oh my god!
要死啦 要死啦
We are gonna die… we are gonna die!
动起来 动起来
Move! move.
跑就对了 跑 跑
Just run… run run.
快跑 快跑
Let's go! go… go!
你跟我开玩笑嘛
Are you kidding me?
神不知 鬼不觉
"slip in - slip out"?
我们以前就没这么干过好吗
This is not what we always do!
楼梯 快上 快上
Stairs! just run! run!
跑 跑 跑
Run! run! run!
小心手雷
Grenade!
我恨你 我恨死你啦
I hate you, I hate you so much!
我从来都没有想过要来这个国度
I never even wanted to come… to this country!
冷静 让我好好想想
Let me think. just let me think.
如果有人听得见的话
If anyone is listening…
这里是L-26 我们遭到猛烈火力压制
…this is l-26, rmj hot!
请求对我方位置实行动态精确打击
Request dynamic precision strike at our mark!
你别跟我说你刚刚叫了空袭
You did not… just called in an air strike!
噢 是的 我 叫 了
Oh… yes… i… did!
你去哪 别丢下我
Where are you going? don't leave me!
哪冒出来这么多人
Where do they keep coming from?
没地方躲了
There is nowhere to go!
噢不 我们要死啦
Oh man we are gonna die!
闭嘴 韦尔 让我思考
Please, Vail! let me think!
都怪你的主意 我们就要玩完了
We are gonna die because of you!
让我思考
Just let me think!
还想什么 还有什么好想的
Think about what? think about what?
我在想
I'm thinking…
什么
What?
我在想
I'm thinking…
你到底在想什么
What are you thinking?
我在想 这次我们可能真的要死了
I'm thinking… we are probably gonna die here.
我就知道
I knew it!
我还活着
I am still alive!
尼克
Nick!
哈拉姆
Haram.
我告诉过你们应该呆在
I was told you boys were supposed.
离这一百英里外的地方
to be a 100 kil from here.
是的长官 但是根据情报显示
Yes, sir! but based on intelligence…
我们有理由相信当地的叛乱分子
…we had reason to believe the insurgents.
抓了当地平民作人质
were holding civilian hostage.
我们得做出抉择
We had to make the call.
是等待三角洲部队增援还是我们两独自执行这次任务
Wait for delta team to respond or go in alone.
这实际上是莫顿中士的主意要潜入进村子里
It was sergeant morton's idea to go in actually!
经过我们的侦查
Only to find out that the villagers.
因为战争疏散 村子里空无一人
are gone seems evacuating.
对 他们可幸运了 但我们就不是了
Yeah lucky for them, not for us.
三角洲特战队 去村子南部设立警戒区
Delta, south side perimeter.
长官 当我们意识到
Sir, when we realized that we were at the.
这是叛乱分子要塞的时候
center of the insurgent’s stronghold.
那时已经太晚了
…it was too late.
随后我们暴露并遭受了敌军猛烈的火力进攻
We were discovered, we started taking on heavy fire.
其次 长官 韦尔下士 太过谦虚去承认了
Well… sir, Corporal Vail here is too humble to admit it…
但是他是那个冒着生命危险来救我的人
But he risked his life to save mine.
事实上 他是个英雄 我推荐他
He is a hero, in fact… i'd like.
来做传讯的口供证人
to recommend him for citation.
我来说说我想的另一套情节
Let me run another scenario by it.
长官 什么意思
Sir?
一个…两个执行远程侦查任务的混球
One in which…two assholes from long range reconnaissance…
说的就是你们
…that would be you…
我们跑遍伊拉克北部
…run all over northern iraq,
就是尽量避免与敌军交火
just one step ahead the enemy.
除此之外 你们也不是来杀敌
Except, instead of hunting for the enemy…
而是来猎宝的
…you hunt for antiquities…
然后把一切可能挖到的宝物
…stealing whatever isn't nailed down.
倒卖到黑市上好大赚一笔
and selling it on the black market.
与此同时 这些狂热分子
Meanwhile, these fanatical insurgents…
又正好想抹去这五千年的历史
…trying to erase 5, 000 years of history…
很不情愿的说 这的确是个不错的幌子
…unwillingly cover your tracks. it's a pretty good scam.
莫顿中士
Sergeant morton!
在哪
Where is it?
什么 什么什么东西在哪
What? where is what?
那封信 那张你从我这偷走的地图
The letter. the map you stole from me.
地图 我不知道你在说些什么
Map? I do not know what you are talking about.
我怎么会
How would i…
我 我甚至都没有
Had even had the opportunity to.
从你那偷东西的机会
steal anything from you.
小姐 怎么称呼
Miss… Miss…
好吧 莫顿中士认为这很难以启齿
Ok… sgt. morton here thinks that.
我觉得也很羞耻
i would be too embarrassed.
不过事实是 三天前
…to tell you that I had him in my hotel room…
在巴格达的一家旅馆里 我们两一起睡过
…3 nights ago, in baghdad.
当我在熟睡时 他偷走了我的东西
And whilst I was sleeping, he went through my things.
我并不感到尴尬 尼克
I'm not embarrassed, nick.
要说恶心 是的 后悔至极 啊 当然
Disgusted? yes. regretful? ah certainly.
不过我对你的「能力」真得是刮目相看
But mainly just amazed, to your ability…
你那套高质量的套路 哇 简直了
…to mimic all the qualities of genuine human intimacy…
这么多前戏 也就坚持了 多久 十五秒
…if only for… 15 seconds?
地图到底在哪 莫顿
Where is the map, morton?
长官 我承认
Sir, I admit that…
我和哈尔西小姐的确是
…miss Halsey and I did spend a.
共度良宵过一次
delightful even.
如果她是真情实感的话
A very long and satisfying evening…
那将会是更加漫长而完美的夜晚
…if her reactions are to be considered sincere.
但是长官 我现在对她的美好回忆已经烟消云散了
But sir, I left with nothing more than fond memories.
或许是因为我第二天早上的
Now, perhaps I may have neglected to.
不辞而别惹怒了她
say goodbye to her the next moring…
只是因为她很疲惫
…only because she was exhausted…
我实在是不想吵醒她 - 好吧
- …and I did not want to wake her. - ok.
我如此亲切关怀竟然落得如此回报
And the reward for my gracious consideration?
长官你看 这就是「最毒妇人心」
Well sir, as you can see "hell hath no fury".
- 长官 - 哦 我的上帝啊
- sir. - oh my god!
这是古埃及的
It's egyptian.
有什么不同寻常的吗
Why is that unusual?
韦尔 我们现在是在波斯湾
We are in the persian gulf, Vail.
是的 这里距离埃及有一千英里 这就不同寻常了
Right. egypt is a 1000 miles away so it's unusual.
都放下吧 快 去把剩下的都搬来
Put those down, hurry. go get the rest.
好的
Got it.
上校 这是个重大的发现
Colonel, this is an significant find.
我需要你的人手将这个村子保护起来
i need your men to secure this village.
可我们甚至都不应该出现在这个地方
We are not even supposed to be here.
我的职责是确保任何有价值的东西
Is my job to make sure that anything.
不会落入敌人之手
of value stays out of enemy hands.
我们对这下面有什么并不是很清楚
We have no idea what could be down there.
当初图坦卡门墓穴中的文物
The content of tutankhamun's tomb alone…
估值6.5亿英镑
…were valued at 650 million pounds sterling.
明白吗
Understand?
上校 恕我直言
Colonel… if I may with a couple shake charges…
我们可以先用炸药把洞口堵上
…we could just close this hole right up,
以后找个好日子再让哈尔西小姐过来
and miss Halsey can cen we're moving out.
- 闭嘴 - 好吧
- shut up. - okay.
你们有两个小时的时间 然后我们就必须马上撤离
You got two hours, then we're moving out.
你们带着他一起下去
You are getting in the hole with him.
- 他 - 我
- him? - me?
是的
Yep.
长官
Sir.
收拾好就出发 这是命令
You gear up, that's an order.
我在路边等你 中士
I'll be right here on the road sarge.
你也跟着下去吧 韦尔
Get in the damn hole, Vail!
噢 大兄弟 别啊
Oh man!
我目前身处于一个大型的前厅
I am in a large antechamber of some kind.
前厅的北墙上刻着几行铭文
There is an inscription on the northern wall.
太阳神 拉 哈拉胡提的祷文
The litany of ra.
你在逗我吗
…kidding me?
都怪你 尼克 都是你的错
Your fault, nick. your fault.
你看到这里有什么宝藏吗 尼克 我可什么都没看到
Do you see any treasure here, nick? because I don't.
你知道我看到什么了吗 我看到
Do you know what I see? I see.
全是些带不走的雕像
statues that I can't carry around.
- 小声点 - 你才小声点
- keep it down. - you keep it down.
你在搞什么
What are you doing?
这绝对是个墓穴
It is definitely a tomb.
这是什么 水银吗
What is that? mercury?
是的
Yeah.
古埃及人相信
The ancient egyptians believed.
这可以抑制邪恶
that it weakened iest of ammon…
但我们如今有了更深入的了解
Well now we know better.
这玩意儿能毒死你
this stuff will kill you.
是啊 就在把你弄疯之后
Yeah, after it makes you crazy.
有水银从天花板上滴下来 再回流到
There is mercury dripping from the ceiling…
地上的洞中
…into holes in the ground.
可能是连接
Possibly to connect the…
这是墓穴内的运河系统
It's a canal system…
汇集流向
…leading all the way to…
把照射灯打开
Get the lights!
哦 上帝啊
Oh my god.
把包里的东西都拿出来
Get everything out of the bags.
我怎么跟你说的
What did I tell you?
好多金子啊 尼克
That's a lot of gold, nick.
我目前在一个与前厅相连的人造大型墓穴中
I am in a large men-made cavern adjoining the antechamber.
显而易见 这里有向下延伸的阶梯
There are chiseled steps descending from the ledge.
墓穴中央有一条运河系统
There is a canal at the center of them…
水银灌满底部的
…that feeds a ritual well at.
祭献深井
the base, filled with mercury.
这个是珠子做成的圣甲虫戒指
Beads of scarabs, scarab signal rings.
它属于底比斯神庙的
This is a high priest of ammon…
一位安蒙神大祭司
…from the temple of the thebes.
水银井周围由宗教性质的锁链包围着
There is a ritual barrier chain that's around the well…
作为对闯入者的警告
…as a warning to intruders.
阻隔他们入内
To keep people out.
这个地下墓穴没有
There isn't a single provision made for.
任何被盗的痕迹
someone's journey into the underworld…
没有坎努帕斯坛 没有陪葬俑
No canopic jars, no shabtis.
被埋葬在这样一个地方
To be buried in a place like this…
真的是比死更难受
…would have been a fate worse than death.
尼克
Nick!
想都别想
Don't even think about it.
有六位守护者面朝井口
There are six watchers around the well…
而并非朝向外边
…facing inward instead of out.
无论这里面有什么
Whatever is in there…
这些锁链都不是为了把它拉出来的
…those chains aren't for bringing it up.
而是在镇压
They are for holding it down.
这不是个坟墓
This is not a tomb.
这是个监狱
It's a prison.
呼叫 L26 请回答
Lima 2-6, come in.
收到 长官
Copy, sir.
马上出来 我们收到报告 有可疑人士入侵
Get out now. we've got reports of bogeys inbound.
我们必须马上撤退
We gotta take off.
告诉格林威 我们必须通知国防安全局
Tell greenway we have to notify d.t.r.a.
为什么
For what?
- 我需要联系开罗的专家 - 开罗
- I need specialists from cairo… - cairo?
密封衣和屏蔽手套
…seaborn suits and shielding cuffs.
珍妮 我们没时间了 你最好现在带上你要带走的东西
Jenny, we are out of time. you better grab what you can now!
我不会走的 除非我看清井里面有什么东西
I'm not leaving until I see what's in that pool.
你得离开这 我们现在要立刻撤退了
Oh you are leaving. we're leaving right now.
我千里迢迢而来不会空手而归的
I have not come this far just to leave without…
嘿 嘿
Hey! hey!
别开枪 韦尔
Cease fire! Vail!
停火 停火
Cease fire! cease fire!
这就是些骆驼蜘蛛 这些蜘蛛没毒性
They are just camel spiders! they're not even poisonous!
我们现在能离开了吗
Can we please, leave?
- 你疯了吗 韦尔 - 快走吧
- are you out of your mind, Vail? - please!
你哪里出了毛病
What is wrong with you?
有东西咬了我的脖子
That thing bit my neck!
- 没事的 没事的 - 它咬了我
- okay… okay. - it bit me!
够了 我不管这些
Enough of this! I don't care!
我要走了 你们随意 反正我是要走了
I'm leaving! with or without you! i'm leaving!
它咬我了 拜托 尼克
It bit me! please, nick!
我们能走了吗
Can we please, leave?
你赐予我自由
You have set me free.
你是我命中注定之人
My chosen.
尼克
Nick!
告诉格林威 让他派人来
Tell greenway he is gonna send a team.
把这东西带走
to get this thin.
不然他就得去解释为什么会把我丢在这里
…or he is gonna have to explain why he left me behind.
照做
Do it!
好的
Okay.
吊上去
Climb by the man!
正在平稳吊移
Climb line is steady.
朝着九点方向过去点
More towards your nine o'clock!
高度30英尺
Holding at 30 feet.
再高一点
A little more.
B队呼叫E队 我们看见猛烈的沙尘暴从
Bishop to echo. we have visual on a severe sandstorm…
西面向E12前进
…heading west to echo 12.
嘿
Hey!
等等 小心点 这可是有五千年历史呢
Wait… wait… please be careful. this is 5, 000 years old.
60秒后起飞 动作快点
60 seconds! in the air! let's go!
小心 小心
Careful, careful.
现在起飞吧
Get us off the ground now!
哈尔西 坐下
Halsey, take a sit!
需要帮助吗
Need some help?
不
No.
- 顺便说句 不用谢 - 我要谢你什么
- you are welcome by the way. - how's that?
因为我救了你 不管怎么说
Because I saved your… whatever it is.
在你投下地狱火弹之前
That was safely hidden for 5, 000 years.
它可是在地底下安安稳稳地藏了5000年
before you dropped a hell-fire missile on it.
那你可能永远都发现不了这里
And you might have never found it otherwise.
再说一次 你不用谢我
Again… you're welcome.
你觉得这个是什么
Do you have any idea what this is?
它的意义是什么
The significance of it?
在美索不达米亚的一座墓穴内发现古埃及石棺
An egyptian sarcophagus in a tomb in mesopotamia.
你为什么说「只有15秒钟」
Why just say "15 seconds"?
什么跟什么
What of what?
你刚才跟格林威说
You told greenway that I can mimic all.
我和你啪啪啪
the qualities of.
15秒就射了
…for 15 seconds.
我的意思是 啊 肯定不止15秒
I mean… uh… it was not 15 seconds.
好了 不管多长时间 这都不是真的
Well, however long it lasted, it wasn't real.
我对你的感觉都是真实的 我从没骗过你
I never lied to you about my feelings.
你偷我东西
You stole from me.
但我没有对你说谎
But I didn't lie.
你是不是从来不会替别人考虑
Do you ever think of anyone but yourself?
这意义重大
This means something.
超乎你想象
Something bigger than you can imagine.
这是我毕生心血
My life's work.
但是你却来偷走了它
And you were going to steal it.
你觉得这东西在黑市上能值多少钱
How much do you think that's worth on the black market?
我是詹妮弗·哈尔西博士
This is Dr. Jennifer Halsey…
我正在对这具古埃及石棺
Conducting a preliminary analysis.
做初步检查
of an egyptian.
这是在伊拉克北部的尼尼微省发现的
…discovered in the nineveh province, northern iraq.
这些象形文字绝对记载着一个新王朝
The hieroglyphs are definitely new kingdom.
墓棺上面记载着王后 梅内普莱因难产而死
It appears that the wife of king menehptre…
留下一个
…died in childbirth…
孩子作为王国的继承人
…leaving a sole heir to the throne…
一个女孩
…a girl…
叫安玛奈特
…called Ahmanet.
下士 你究竟在搞什么鬼
Corporal, what in the living hell are you doing son?
韦尔
Vail?
韦尔下士
Corporal Vail?
该死的
Dammit.
韦尔下士 你听到我跟你说
Corporal Vail, do you hear me talking.
什么了吧 我说 放下刀
to you? I said! drop it now!
韦尔
Vail, just…
韦尔 哇哦 哇哦
Vail! wow… wow!
韦尔
Vail!
不 见鬼了 韦尔
Oh my god. Vail!
放下武器 立刻放下武器
Drop the weapon! drop it now!
立刻
Now!
拜托 拜托
Please… please…
立刻放下武器
Drop it now!
- 放下枪 - 把它扔掉
- put the gun down! - drop it!
放下武器 放下 坐回去
Put down the weapon! put it down… back off…
住手 不能在加压了的机舱开枪
Stop! do not shoot! this is a pressurized aircraft!
尼克
Nick.
韦尔
Vail.
- 韦尔 把刀放下 - 韦尔
- Vail, put the knife down. - Vail.
- 韦尔 不 - 韦尔
- Vail, no. - Vail!
韦尔
Vail!
韦尔 停 停 韦尔 韦尔
Ehy Vail! stop! stop! Vail… Vail!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
故障 故障 故障
Pan-pan-pan.
这是N4-0-9-9
This is november 4-0-9-9.
美国空军C-130大力神运输机
United states c-130 hercules.
- 发生了什么事 - 做好扣紧安全带
- what's happening? - take your sit and strap in.
- 我们在英国上空 - 英国
- …over england. - england?
现在我也不知道发生了什么事 坐好
Right now I don't know what's happening. take your sit!
两个引擎都失灵了
We lost thrust in both engines.
无线电失联 正从12000英尺骤降 离爱丁堡机场280英里
No way to our contact. dropping to 12, 000, 280 on the edi.
这是什么鬼
What the hell is that?
快跑 快跑 快跑
Go! go! go!
降落伞
Parachute!
我不会用
I do not know how to do this!
珍妮 你能做到 的 你能行
Jenny, you can do this! you can do this!
把你的手给我
Give me your hand!
哈尔西小姐
Miss Halsey.
哈尔西小姐 你准备好了吗
Miss Halsey, do you think you're up to it.
对不起 什么
I'm sorry. what?
我们需要你来帮忙辨认下尸体
We need your help identifying the body.
身份不明
Unknown.
韦尔
Vail!
嘿 伙计
Hey buddy.
你他妈的吓死我了
You scared the shit out of me.
我们需要谈谈 尼克
We need to talk, nick.
发生了什么事
What's happening?
你知道发生了什么
You know what's happening.
我死了吗
Am I dead?
死
Dead?
你没死 但是你还不如死了好
No. but you are gonna wish you were.
请这边走
Come on this way, please.
哦 我的天啊 尼克
Oh my god! nick.
珍
Jen.
发生了什么事 我在哪里
What's happening? where am i?
谁是这里的负责人
Who's in charge here?
基地 这里是搜救一队
Base, this is search team one.
我们似乎找到了坠机残骸
Looks like the trail of wreckage…
残骸散落在方圆2-2.5英里的森林里
…it's spread across 2-2, 5 half miles through the forest.
正派人到埃尔斯福德港 待命
Coming up on the aylestord pier now. standby.
码头上有件残骸 看上去
The pier is a wreck. it looks like.
像是部分机翼 是一台涡轮机发动机
a part of the wing.A turbine.
距离坠机主要现场几英里 完毕
Miles away from the primary crash site. over.
收到 这里是搜救一队 收到信息
Copy, search team one. message received.
找到一具尸体 已经没用生命迹象 待命
One body found. no obvious signs of life. standby.
伤员确认死亡
Casualty confirmed deceased.
请派医护人员到场 完毕
Requesting attendance of ambulance personnel. over.
搜救一队收到
Copy, search team one.
医疗队已出发 完毕
Ambulance staff now on route. over.
这 这是什么鬼
What… what the hell…?
嘿 你们最好能过来一下
Hey! you better come in to…
艾伦
Allen?
你还好吗
You alright?
艾伦
Allen!
天啊
Jesus!
起来吧
Rise.
一架美国军机今晚在苏里市坠毁
A US military plane crash landed in surrey this evening…
韦弗利修道院差一点就被殃及
…just missing waverley abbey.
即时新闻 威弗尼修道院地区
美国军用飞机坠毁
你是怎么逃出飞机的
How did you get out of that plane?
你连点儿轻伤都没有
There's not a single scratch on your body.
是的
Yeah.
谢谢你
Thank you.
为什么谢我
For what?
你救了我
You saved my life.
换做你 你也会为我做同样的事
You would have done the same for me.
尼克
Nick.
听着 尼克
Listen, nick.
我想你可能知道了什么
I think you should know something.
你知道我和一个考古专家小组工作
You know I work with a group of archaeologists.
- 嗯 - 是的
- yeah. - well…
我们有一个这样的推测
…we developed this theory…
有一个古埃及公主
…that an egyptian princess had been.
在历史书上被抹掉了
erased from the history book.
是故意的
…deliberately.
我们一直寻找一个叫做
We've been searching for something.
赛斯之刃的东西
called "the darue in england.
一把顶端嵌着红宝石的祭祀刀
A ceremonial knife with a large jewel at the hilt.
赛斯是古埃及的死神
Seth is the egyptian god of death.
据传说记载 将刀石合一
And legend has it that the dagger and the stone, together…
就能让赛斯化为真身
…had the power to give seth physical form.
我认为它被藏在欧洲这
I'm convinced it was hidden here, in europe.
是在几个世纪之前被十字军盗走的
Stolen by crusaders centuries ago.
我在一个十字军骑士的手稿里
I found reference to it in a manuscript.
得到了相关记录
written by a crue in england.
上面说匕首与红宝石被拆开了
That suggested the dagger was broken apart.
这位骑士带着红宝石被
That the stone buried with this knight…
一起安葬于英国的某个地方
…somewhere here in england.
最近在伦敦发现了一个大型的
A massive crusader tomb, was.
十字军墓穴
recently discoversaw those birds.
我们相信红宝石就藏在那的某个地方
We believe that the stone is in there somewhere.
正是这个墓穴让我们找到了安玛奈特
That tomb is what led us to Ahmanet.
我认为她就是记载中的那个公主
I think she is the princess in the legend.
这些象形文字说是她谋杀了她的父亲
The hieroglyphics said that she murdered her father.
- 谋杀 - 还有她父亲的孩子
- murdered? - along with his child.
她与死神签订了某种契约
She made some sort of pact with the god of death.
而且后来 当我看到那些鸟
And then, when I saw those birds…
还有沙尘暴
…and that sandstorm…
我就感觉到大事不妙
whatever I mean something is happening.
你活下来了 但是我不知道为什么
You are alive I do not know how.
你 我 出去
You… i… go…
抱歉 尼克 我想我们惹怒了神灵
I'm sorry, nick. I think we angered the gods.
容我失陪一下
Can you excuse me?
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
请表明身份
Identify, please.
我是詹妮弗 帮我转接亨利
This is Jenny. get me Henry.
詹妮弗
Jennifer.
这个问题比我们
This is a far more significant.
想象的严重多了
problem than we have ever imagined.
出大事了 亨利 我很担心他
Something is happening, Henry. i'm worried about him.
派你的人到伦敦来
Bring your soldier to London. do not.
别再和他深入谈论了
Do not discuss anything further with him.
明白吗
Understand?
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
珍妮看起来很不错
Jenny looks good.
- 好的 这不是真的 - 真到不能再真了
- ok this isn't happening. - I mean really great.
好吧 你停下吧
Ok. really stop.
你知道吗 我一直认为我和她是有机会的
You know I always thought I had a chance with her.
- 什么 - 你怎么可以这么渣
- what? - how do you squander that?
肯定是墓地里的水银蒸汽
There was mercury in that tomb. vapors.
你怎么把它搞砸的
How did you mess that up?
这是我的幻觉
It's just in my head.
不 这是真的
No it's not.
你朝我开枪
You shot me.
等等 什么 等下等下等下 你
Wait. what… wait wait wait you…you.
你
You…
你刺死了格林威
…you stabbed greenway.
- 我救了你 - 你杀了他
- I saved you. - you murdered him.
然后你就向我开枪了
And you shot me.
你想杀我 你真是想杀珍妮
You tried to kill me. you even went after jenny.
你向我开枪了 三枪
You shot me. three times.
是的
Yes.
三次 尼克
Three times, nick.
第三次没必要的
The third one was unnecessary.
你吓坏我了 我失控了
You freaked me out. I panicked.
我很抱歉 好吗
I'm sorry. okay?
不好
Not okay.
看着我 看着我的脸
Look at me. look at my face.
我被诅咒了 尼克 你也是
I'm cursed nick, and you are cursed.
只有一种方式破除诅咒
And there is only one way to break it.
那就是完成她要你做的事情
You're going to do exactly what she wants…
不然咱俩全吃不了兜着走
…or this is gonna get a lot worse for both of us.
你说我被诅咒了是什么意思
What do you mean i'm cursed?
对不起
Sorry.
啊 就 在给我一分钟的时间 谢谢你们了
Just… uh… give me a minute. thank you.
顺便说下你进的是女厕所
You walked into the chicks bathroom by the way.
去你自己的洗手间
Go to your own bathroom!
是的 是女厕所
Yes, it's the ladies room.
你说我被诅咒了是什么意思
What do you mean i'm cursed?
你认为你是怎么从空难中活下来的
How do you think you survived the crash?
「史特派尔」
"setapai".
你知道这是什么意思吧
You know what it means.
她有个关于你的计划 尼克
She's got plans for you, nick.
计划
Plans?
你逃不掉的
You can't run away.
你也无处可逃
You can't escape.
帮帮我
Help me!
从路中间滚开 傻瓜
Get out of the road, wanker!
尼克
Nick!
你到底在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
我想你是对的
I think you were right.
- 我们惹怒了神灵 - 等等 什么
- we angered the gods. - wait… what?
我看到她了 在棺木里的那个人
I saw her… the chick in the box.
- 安玛奈特 - 那个
- Ahmanet? - that one.
- 尼克 - 他说我被诅咒了
- nick… - he said i'm cursed.
- 谁说的 - 韦尔
- who said? - Vail.
- 韦尔 - 我们发现的那口棺材的
- Vail? - the coffin we found.
- 是石棺 - 管他什么的
- sarcophagus. - whatever.
那上面有字
There was writing on it.
是象形文字
Hieroglyphics.
珍妮 说真的 我现在对
Jenny, respectfully, i'm not interested.
考古术语不感兴趣
in archeological jargon right now.
我们带出墓穴的棺材上刻着文字
The writing on the box that we took out of the hole.
是的 抱歉
Yes, sorry.
这是有关诅咒的东西
There was something about a curse in.
那玩意儿还在吗 找到了吗
there, was it there？was it there?
尼克 你有点脑震荡
Nick, you've had a concussion.
- 是有点 - 暴露在毒气（汞蒸气）中太久了
- yes. - toxic exposure.
那你解释 我为什么会知道「史特派尔」的意思是命定之人
How dose that explain that I know that "Aetapai"means"my chosen".
- 这是古埃及文 - 是古埃及文
- it's ancient egyptian. - ancient egyptian.
我怎么会知道
How do I know that?
你在中东呆了很多年
You've been in the middle east for years.
什么 不
What? no!
你肯定听过 只不过你忘记了
You heard it… you forgot it…
你为什么就是不相信我 我告诉你
Why are you backing off from this? i'm telling you.
她活过来了
She is real.
尼克
Nick.
尼克 你怎么了
Nick… what is it?
我想你是对的
I think you're right.
我 脑袋里一团麻
I… this is all in my head.
你能找到那个棺材吗 打开看看
Can't you find the box, look inside.
当我看到一个三千岁的木乃伊在里面时
…and when I see a 3, 000 years old prune in there…
- 尼克 - 我就相信没诅咒了
- nick. - …no more curse.
你不需要石棺 你需要看医生
You don't need a sarcophagus, you need a doctor.
我知道一个人
I know someone.
是伦敦的一个专家
A specialist in London.
别告诉我说你也不想去看看
Don't tell me that you don't want to see it too.
你的毕生心血 拜托啊 珍妮
Your life's work, come on Jenny.
我想我知道它在哪里
I think I know where it is.
C8-1报告基地
Charlie 8-1 the base.
我们到达坠机现场 在威弗利修道院以北四百米处
We are at impact site, 400m north of waverley abbey.
消防员控制火势
Firefighters control the fire…
尼克
Nick.
尼克 你要去哪
Nick! where are you going?
坠毁地点不是那里 你要去哪
The crash isn't up that way. where are you going?
我们的方向是对的
We are in the right place.
尼克
Nick.
Nick!
我实在搞不懂我们要在这里干嘛
I do not know what we're doing here.
石棺不在这里
This isn't the right place.
就在这里
Yes it is.
不 不在这
No it isn't.
主要的坠毁地带在那边
The main crash site it's up that way…
石棺也在那
…and so is my artifact.
那才是我们要去的地方
And that's where we are going.
见鬼
What the hell?
我怎么
How did i…?
珍妮
Jenny?
尼克
Nick?
好的
Ok.
什么
What?
死神
God of death…
抱歉 你说什么
I'm sorry. what?
赛斯的力量
Powerful seth…
请进入这个凡人的肉体
…i welcome you into this mortal body…
不
No.
跟我融为一体
Unite to me finally.
珍妮
Jenny!
啊
Yeah?
快跑
Run!
快走 快走
Come on! come on!
尼克
Nick!
喂 喂
Hey! hey!
不 不 不
No! no! no!
嘿 尼克 不
Hey! Nick! no!
尼克
Nick!
你刚准备抛下我
Were you just gonna leave me?
你看见了 是吗
You saw that, right?
你竟然要抛下我
You were gonna leave me!
- 你看见了 是吗 - 我怎么可能没看见
- you saw it, right? - I can't unsee it!
我们要去哪
Where are we going?
离开这里 前面有条高速公路
Away from here. there's a highway up ahead.
- 你怎么知道 - 我就是知道
- how do you know? - I know.
我的天 你知道这都是些什么吗
Oh my god. do you realize what this is?
赛斯之刃
It's the dagger of seth.
她刚准备用这东西刺穿我
She was gonna drive that thing right through me.
那块宝石 不见了
The stone, it is missing.
是的 看起来好像把她激怒了
Yeah, it seems to have really pissed her off.
是真的
It's real.
怎么会在那座雕像里
How was in that statue?
那雕像是个圣器
That statue was a reliquary.
十字军用它们来隐藏圣物
Crusaders have been using them to hide holy relics.
但她知道宝石就在那
But she knew it was there.
你的意思是她故意
You are saying that she brought.
让飞机坠毁在教堂附近
the plane down thgo to the church.
这解释了为什么她想让你来教堂
That's why she wanted you to come to the church.
她想让我来这座教堂
She wanted me to go to the church?
我告诉过你是我想来教堂的
I told you that I wanted to go to church.
我告诉过你 我说的是 我想看
I told you… I said… that I wanted to see…
- 我想看她的尸体 - 看她的尸体
- I wanted to see her corpse. - see her corpse.
尼克 她就在你脑子里
Nick she is in your head.
你在说什么 那
What are you talking about? that…
那简直太可笑了
that is ridiculous because I…
我怎么把车开回来了
I drove right back to her.
天呐 她真的在我脑子里
Oh my god she is in my head.
走 走 走 走 走
Go go go go go!
快把它弄走
Get it off of me!
狗杂种
Son of a bitch!
那是我的脸 是我的脸
That's my face! that's my face!
抱歉
Sorry!
尼克
Nick!
珍妮
Jenny?
Jenny.
尼克
Nick!
好吧
Okay.
Alright.
干掉她 尼克
Get her, nick!
干掉她 干掉她
Get her! get her!
打死她
Kick her ass!
第二分队 快
Phase two! quick!
将她往后拉
Pull her back!
突击队行动
Delta team move!
将目标击倒
Bring the target down!
你是谁
Who are you?
你们要带我去哪
Where are you taking me?
发生了什么
What's happening?
在这待着
Stay.
不必约束
Make yourself comfortable.
你他妈是谁
Who the hell are you?
我是谁
Who am i?
更重要的问题是 莫顿先生
The more relevant question, Mr. Morton…
你到底是谁
Who exactly are you?
理论上 我了解你的一切
In theory, I know all about you.
武装侦查兵 受过表彰
Army reconnaissance, decorated soldier…
但这里一页页都是
…and page after page indicating a.
你的种种劣迹
deep and troubling.
不过 这些文件对于我
But you see, this file contains.
一点价值都没有
nothing of any real value to me.
这就是为什么我想跟你面对面谈谈
That's why I wanted to see you face to face.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是一名博士
I am a doctor.
博士
Doctor.
研究化学病理学以及神经外科
Chemical pathology, neurosurgery.
是皇家学会成员
member of the Royal Society.
我还是个律师
I am also a lawyer.
我的名字叫哲基尔
My name is Jekyll.
亨利·哲基尔博士
Dr. Henry Jekyll.
知道了吧
There you are.
这些天 我在研究免疫学
This days, I specialize in immunology, perhaps.
以及流行病学
Infectious diseases perhaps.
我想 如果可以的话 莫顿先生
I would like to, if I may, Mr. Morton…
告诉你一个故事
…to tell you a story.
我一个病人的故事
A story about a patient of mine.
一个信守诺言的人
A man of promise.
一个相信自己无可挑剔的人
A man who believed he was beyond reproach…
直到他病了
…until he got ill.
这种病开始会通过一些细微的地方表现出来
The disease manifested itself in subtle ways at first.
但情况会逐渐恶化
And then it grew…
直到成为一种毁灭性
…into an overwhelming desire…
不可抑制的
…an unquenchable thirst…
力量
…for chaos.
给他人带来灾难
For the suffering of others.
他很幸运
He was quite fortunate.
他自己就是个医生
He himself was a physician.
如果邪恶是一种病原体 那就有理由
And if evil were a pathogen, to be reasoned…
能够将它治愈
…then there must surely be a cure.
我想 如果可以的话 莫顿先生
I would like to, if I may, Mr. Morton…
给你看些东西
…to show you something.
身份识别中
哲基尔.H.
欢迎来到博见部 莫顿先生
Welcome to prodigium, Mr. Morton.
源自拉丁语
From the latin, "monstrum vel prodigium".
一个有关怪兽的警告
"a warning of monsters".
忘掉你之前的认知
Forgive the state of things.
我们几乎没时间为我们的客人做准备
We had very little time to prepare for our guest.
只有珍妮弗提供的信息才能继续下去
And only the information Jennifer provided to go on.
事实上 她为我们工作
In truth, she works for us.
这件事并没有经过精准的科学推论
It's not an exact science, this business.
这件事是
And the business being?
邪恶的 莫顿先生
Evil, Mr. Morton.
公认的 可控的 经检测的 具有毁灭性的
Recognized, contained, examined, destroyed.
她是 我们至今遇到过的最古老的邪灵
She is, by far, the most ancient we have ever encountered.
你们对她做了什么
What are you doing to her?
给她注射汞
Embalming her with mercury.
到零下38度的时候
At - 38 degrees…
她血管中的汞就会凝固
…the mercury in her veins will solidify…
到时候解剖她就没什么问题了
…and she should be safe for dissection then.
解剖 你说过我们只是研究她
Dissection? you said that we'd study her.
是的 通过解剖来研究
Yes, by dissection.
但她是古埃及那段鲜为人知历史
But she is a living witness to.
唯一活着的见证者
a history that we barely know.
她是个威胁 珍妮弗
She is a threat, Jennifer.
等等 等等 这关我什么事
Hold on, hold on. so… where does that leave me?
你被诅咒了 莫顿先生
Cursed, Mr. Morton.
你得的可不是普通的感冒
This is not some common cold you have.
一点鸡汤睡上一个好觉
Some chicken soup and a good night.
并不能治好你的病
sleep will not make it go away.
你已经被选中
You have been selected…
作为一个终极邪灵的容器
…as the vessel for the ultimate evil.
只有我们才能帮助你
And we are the only ones who can rectify that.
你无法改变你的命运
You cannot change your fate.
诅咒永远也不会被破解
The curse will never be broken.
我上一个选中的人已经被杀
My chosen one was murdered.
你会接替他
You will take his place.
既然你选中了他
But if you choose him…
别
No.
为什么你要杀了他
Why were you going to kill him?
我没打算杀他
I was not going to kill him.
我是想要给他
I was going to give him…
永生
…eternal life.
让他成为神祇在世
Make it a living god.
你杀了你的父亲
You murdered your father.
我全心全意
I loved my father…
爱着我的父亲
…with all my heart.
我只想让他也一样爱我
I only wanted his love in return.
你杀了他的妻子
You killed his wife.
他们的孩子
Their child.
今非昔比 情非得已
They were different times.
我们的觉醒之日就要来临
The day of the awakening will soon be upon us.
你会成为赛斯
You will become seth.
世界会掌控在你手中
The world will fall to your desire.
你将掌握生死之权
You will have power of life over death.
你还会拥有我
And you will have me.
我会成为你的女王
I will be your queen.
妥协吧
Just give in.
尼克
Nick.
尼克 醒醒
Nick, wake up.
醒醒
Wake up.
他们会杀了你
They will kill you…
就像他们杀死上一个命定之人一样
…just as they killed my chosen before you.
好烫
It burns.
什么
What?
好烫
It burns!
住手
Stop it!
停下
Stop!
住手
Stop it!
停下
Stop!
真有趣
Fascinating.
我应该怎么跟你解释呢
What was I supposed to tell you?
如果我说这个地方真实存在
Would you even have believed me if.
你还会相信我吗
i said that this place was real?
亨利找到我的时候
When Henry came to me…
我因为和他们志同道合而接下了这份工作
…i took the job because we had a common interest.
所有你俩是相互利用的关系
So you are using each other.
现在她就在利用你
Now, she's using you.
看啊
Look.
不管你怎么想
Despite what you might think…
不管我
…despite my…
的判断有多客观
…my better judgment…
我在乎你
…i care about you.
内心深处 奋勇突围
Somewhere in there, fighting to get out…
你是个好人
…is a good man.
你什么都不知道
You don't know that.
我知道
I do.
怎么会
How?
你在飞机上救了我的命
You saved my life on that plane.
你毫不犹豫就把唯一的降落伞给了我
You gave me the only parachute without hesitation.
我还以为不止一把呢
I thought there was another one.
莫顿先生
Mr. morton.
要喝一杯吗
Drink?
我想我这里有你喜欢的
I think I found something.
你所见
What you have seen…
你所识
What you must know…
我研究过古神灵的语言
I have studied the word of the old gods.
古神灵
The old gods?
你们的语言太简单了
Your language is simple.
你们真正想知道的
What you truly wish to know…
是死亡面纱背后的谎言
…is what lies beyond the veil of death.
想知道我曾看到的一切吗
To know what I have seen?
是的
Yes.
你会看到的
And you will…
当我杀死你的时候
…when I kill you.
他们找到了宝石
They have found the stone.
你把我选中的人带来这里
You brought my chosen here.
你猜他们现在要对他做什么
What do you think they will do with him now?
欢迎来到新世界
Welcome to a new world…
神灵和怪物的世界
…of gods and monsters.
恶魔有很多名字 莫顿先生
Evil has many names, mr. morton.
比如说被称为赛斯
Take seth, for example.
它是古埃及人眼中的死神
Known to egyptians as the god of death.
在旧约中他还被称为撒旦 路西法
In the old tastament:Satan, lucifer.
- 都是恶魔 - 是的
- the devil. - quite so.
没错 很坏很坏 都得
Yeah. bad… bad… gotta…
你看 恶魔是存在于我们世界
You see evil is the shadow that.
之外的阴影
exists just outside our world.
不断寻找方法进来
…continuously searching for a way to come in…
只为转化成血肉之躯
…for a way to become flesh and blood.
但是 我们也不会坐以待毙
Either… we wait for that day to arrive…
我们用自己的方式与他们对抗
…or we can fight it on our own terms.
所以我找到了你
Which brings me to you.
我 是的 我明白 博士
Me? yeah, great, yes… doc.
你说你可以解除我的诅咒
You said that you could cure me.
彻底摆脱
of this curse.Get rid of it.
那么 我们赶快行动吧
So, let's do it doc.
你的计划是什么
What's your plan?
莫顿先生 这事可能有点复杂
Mr. morton, these things are complex.
是的 我知道 我知道
Yeah? I bet, I bet.
当你要处理人类的救赎时
When one is dealing with the salvation of humanity…
恐怕要做出一点牺牲
…certain sacrifices must be made.
先生 抱歉
Excuse me, sir.
他们找到了
They found it.
找到什么了 什么
What found… what?
亨利
Henry.
你是打算杀了他么
Are you planning on killing him?
杀了他
Kill him?
- 詹妮弗 - 杀了谁
- Jennifer… - kill who?
莫顿先生自一开始弄断锁链
Mr. morton here essentially killed himself…
的时候就已经在劫难逃了
…when he severed the barrier chain…
是他解除了安玛奈特身上五千年的封印
…that had kept Ahmanet power imprisoned for 5, 000 years.
他被选为她最理想的候选人
He was chosen as her ideal candidate.
一个身强体壮 无比狡猾
A thief, physically capable, compulsively devious…
没有灵魂的小偷
…and utterly devoid of soul.
- 什么 - 什么
- what? - what?
这真疯狂
That's insane.
你是想把宝石镶嵌在
Do you want to put the stone in.
匕首上 然后给他来一刀
the dagger and stab him with it?
匕首会让赛斯进入到他体内
The dagger will allow seth to enter his body.
然后我们就能彻底毁灭它了
And then we obliterate it.
等等 等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait.
你想要用那玩意儿捅死我 还是故意的
Do you want to stab me with that thing? intentionally?
古埃及人就是这么干的
Precisely what the egyptians should have done.
你看他们打断了进行中的仪式
You see, they interrupted a ritual in process…
这样的错我们不能
…and that is mistake we cannot…
要避免再犯
…afford to repeat.
- 这就是你的计划 - 亨利
- that's the plan? - Henry…
你不能这样做
…you can't possibly do this.
这就是你的计划
That's your plan?
多米诺骨牌已经开始到下
The dominoes are already falling.
我们没多少时间了
We haven't much time.
不幸的是 我们必须要冒这个险
Unfortunately, it is a risk we must take.
这真是你的计划吗
That's really your plan?
你听到安玛奈特怎么说的了 你的诅咒无法破除
You heard Ahmanet. your curse cannot be broken.
我真的很抱歉 莫顿先生 不管我做什么
I am truly sorry, mr. morton. No matter what I do.
你都是死路一条
you are going to die.
是的 邪恶就是一种瘟疫
Yes, evil is a disease.
一种致命的瘟疫感染
A pestilent pustulant infection…
会腐蚀我们的灵魂
…borrowing its way into our souls.
这个世界需要解药
The world needs a cure.
而你就是那味药
You can be that cure.
停
Stop.
牺牲自己拯救世界
A sacrifice for the greater good!
我对此根本就不感兴趣
I'm not interested in that at all.
好吧
Okay.
- 不 - 把注射器给我
- don't! - give me the injector.
我们停下来休息一会儿
We are just gonna take a minute…
然后我们可以商量出一个新的计划
…and we are all gonna come up with a new plan.
我们现在得走了
We have to go.
你知道你干了什么好事吗
You don't know what you are doing.
是吗 我很清楚我在做什么
Really? I know exactly what i'm doing.
哦 我亲爱的亨利·杰奇
Oh my dear Henry jekyll…
要说我曾在你的新朋友的脸上
…if ever i've seen satan signature upon a face…
看见撒旦的印记
…is on that of your new friend.
嘿 嘿 嘿 拿着这个
Hey, hey hey! take it!
现在
Now!
- 快跑 莫顿先生 - 什么
- run, mr. morton. - what?
快跑
Run!
尼克 开门
Nick! open the door!
你别想了
You don't want that.
住手 珍妮
Stop, Jenny!
住手
Stop!
他们不会放我出去的 尼古拉斯 他们不会放我出去的
They won't let me out, nicholas. they never do.
哇哦 哇哦 这都是什么事
Woah woah what's happening?
你把水银关掉了
did you just shut down the mercury.
皮特
Pete?
你还是太年轻了
You are a younger man…
你必须要学会警惕像我这样的人
…but you must learn to be wary of a man like me.
不是我想杀你 是亨利想杀你
It's not me that wants to kill you, it's Henry.
此刻我有个合作的想法 我明白
I have something more collaborative to that moment.I know it.
和我合作吧
I'm offering you a partnership.
你 是恶魔的化身 我 是你的好朋友 艾迪·海德
You, evil incarnate. me, your good friend, eddie hyde.
想想吧
Think about it.
珍妮
Jenny!
拜托
Come on.
珍妮 住手
Jenny, stop!
拜托 孩子 想想吧
Come on, son. think about it.
我集混乱与毁灭于一身
I am chaos, destruction.
女人们会拜倒在我们的牛仔裤下
The ladies will love us.
来这里
Come here.
我实在是享受你痛苦的表情
I do enjoy the garments of pain.
好样的 莫顿先生 好样的
Well done, mr. morton. well done.
拜托 我们得毁掉宝石
Come on. we have to destroy the stone.
什么
What?
没有宝石 没有仪式
No stone, no ritual.
没有仪式
No ritual…
- 就没有诅咒 - 是的 我知道在那里
- …no curse. - yes. I know where it is.
- 等等 等等 哪条路可以出去 - 我不知道
- Just wait, wait, which way out? - I don't know.
死神
God of death…
将我选中的人带来
Bring forth my chosen…
我召唤埃及之沙
I summon the sands of egypt…
受我召唤
Take me in!
把他带回来
Deliver him to me!
喂
Hello?
她逃跑了 拿走了匕首
She's out! she has the dagger.
我们认为她向你们那边过去了 我们随后就到
We thinks she is coming to you, so are we.
锁上门 保护好宝石
Lock your doors and secure that stone.
尼克
Nick!
尼克 我们快走
Nick, let's go!
我知道宝石在哪里
I know where the stone is!
我们快走
Let's go!
哇哦 这真刺激
Wow, that was intense!
好吧 跟我来
Okay, follow me.
我们在去十字军墓室的路上
We are headed to the crusader burial chamber.
我们从西边的
We'll make our entry through the.
隧道进去 完毕
northwest train tunnels, over.
到时候了 尼克
This is the moment, nick.
时间到了
This is the moment!
是的 你说的对极了
Yes, you are damn right.
我要把你和宝石一起给安玛奈特
I'm gonna taking that stone, deliver you to Ahmanet…
然后我的使命就结束了
…and then my work here is done.
什么
What?
尼克
Nick?
珍妮
Jenny?
嘿 宝贝
Hey, buddy.
安玛奈特是不会放过她的
Ahmanet is never going to let her live.
你救不了她
You can't save her.
起来吧 我的战士们 听我命令
Arise, my warriors, and serve me.
不 哦 不
No! oh no!
尼克
Nick?
你不应该出现在这里
You shouldn't be here.
我跟你过来的
I followed you!
快走 快走 快走
Go go go!
我们还好吗
We are okay?
- 我们在哪里了 - 我不知道
- where are we? - I don't know.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
- 我很害怕 - 看着我
- i'm scared. - just look at me.
我们能行的
We are gonna figure this out.
我只是想和你呆在一起 求求你
Just, I need you to just stay with me, please.
我们能搞定的
We are gonna figure this out…
我要你呆在我身边
i need you to just stay with me.
和我呆在一起 我们能想出办法的
Just stay with me. we'll think of something.
不 珍妮
No! jenny!
珍妮 不
Jenny! no!
不
No!
我们走
Let go!
珍妮
Jenny!
不
No!
不要责备自己
Don't blame yourself.
她注定难逃此劫
She was always doomed.
还有比死更可怕的命运
There are worse fates than death.
来我这里
Come to me.
会有点疼
It hurts.
我知道
I know.
让我消除你的痛苦
Let me take pain away.
臣服于我
Give in to me.
臣服吧
Give in.
当一切结束的时候
When it's over…
你会感谢我
…you will thank me.
我敢保证
I promise.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我们不会有结果的
We are just never gonna happen.
不是因为我
And it's not me.
是你
It's you.
小偷
Thief.
等等
Wait!
毁掉宝石
Destroy the stone…
这一切都完了
…and all is lost.
你会成为神祇在世
You will be a living god.
你将掌控生死
You will have power of life over death.
把它交给我
Give it to me…
我的命定之人
…my chosen.
把它交给我
Give it to me…
我的爱人
…my love.
内心深处
Somewhere in there…
我知道你是个好人
…i know you're a good man.
这个世界需要解药
The world needs a cure.
你就是这味药
You can be that cure.
牺牲自己拯救世界
A sacrifice for the greater good!
珍妮
Jenny.
醒醒
Wake up.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
对不起 珍妮
I'm sorry, jenny.
珍妮
Jenny.
珍妮 拜托醒醒
Jenny, please wake up.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不知道我做了什么
I do not know what i'm doing.
拜托醒醒吧
Please wake up.
珍妮
Jenny.
醒过来啊 求你了
Wake up, please.
快
Just…
珍妮 快醒醒
Jenny, just wake up!
尼克
Nick?
Nick!
尼克
Nick.
Nick?
住手
Stop!
停下来 拜托
Stop. please.
我不知道我现在是什么
I don't know what I am.
我不想伤害你 珍妮
I don't want to hurt you, jenny.
你还活着
You are alive.
看到你活过来我真高兴
I'm so glad you're alive.
哦 尼克
Oh nick.
你做这些是为了我
You did this for me?
是的
Yes.
我做了很多
I have made so many…
很多错事
…many mistakes.
但是这次
But not this time.
不该是你
Not you.
我不想伤害你
I don't want to hurt you.
我永远不想伤害你
I never wanted to hurt you.
你不会的
You won't.
我们没想过事情会变成这个样子
We didn't see this coming, did we?
他们来找我了
They are coming for me.
我真希望我们还有时间
I wish we had more time.
我会找到你的
I'll find you.
再见 珍妮
Goodbye, jenny.
你看错尼克了
You were wrong about nick.
他为了救我牺牲了自己
He gave his life to save me.
就为了把我救回来
To bring me back.
是的 詹妮弗
Yes, Jennifer.
他找到了自己的救赎
He found his redemption.
但是代价如此之高
But at great cost.
他现在是怪物了
He is a monster now.
他还是个人
He is also still a man.
一个好人
A good man.
也许吧
Perhaps.
现在开始探索他的能力了
Yet it has only begun to discover his power.
我们不知道哪股力量可以获胜
And we cannot know which side will win out.
在黑暗与光明之间
Between darkness and light…
在善良与邪恶之间
…good or evil.
嘿 尼克
Hey, nick.
尼克
Nick.
我真高兴能在这里呆着
I'm really glad to be here.
我的意思是 谢谢你帮我
I mean, thank you for bringing me.
复活及这一切 尼克
back to life and everything Nick.
但是我们来这里干嘛
…but what are we even doing here?
我们要去哪里
Where are we going?
拜托 我的老伙计
Come on, my friend.
你的冒险精神去了哪里
Where is your sense of adventure?
哦 不
Oh no.
不管他的身上还有多少人性
Whatever human part of him remains…
会踏遍世界
…will search the world over…
找到方法打破诅咒
…for a way to break the curse.
去找到解药
To find the cure.
恶魔永远不会作罢
Yet evil never rests.
你要时刻记着
And you will call to them…
永远记着
…always.
亨利 他用自己的力量阻止了安玛奈特
Henry, he used his power to stop Ahmanet.
你比任何人更明白他能成为我们强大的盟友
You know more than anyone he could be our greatest ally.
也许吧
Perhaps.
也许是时候让一个怪物
Sometimes it does take a monster…
去迎战另外一个怪物了
…to fight a monster.